(Raj:)So anyway, last night on video chat, I spent,
like, 20 minutes just staring into Lucy's eyes.
(Leonard:)- That sounds romantic.
- It was, until I realized the screen had frozen.
(Raj:)Still one of my top three dates of all time.
So we ever gonna hang out with this girl?
Ahh, I'd love that, but she's not
really comfortable around people.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I used to be uncomfortable
around people, but then I learned a trick.
(Sheldon:)I pretend everyone I meet
is a beloved character from Star Trek.
How's that working for you?
(Sheldon:)Oh, like a charm,
unnamed crewman in a red shirt.
Leonard, I may have gotten you ajob.
- I have ajob.
- Yes, he does. He caters to my every whim.
(Howard:)No, in a couple of weeks, Stephen Hawking's
team is sending an expedition...
(Howard:)...to the North Sea to test
hydrodynamic simulations of black holes.
(Howard:)One of their experimental physicists
dropped out and I recommended you.
(Leonard:)Well, do you really think I have a shot?